Kathi Huzaifa

Flutter Developer

My name is Huzaifa Kathi. I recently Working in Webilok IT Services as a Flutter Developer. I have 1.2 Years of Experience in Flutter Development, from Basic to Advanced Level of Coding. I already Working in GetX State-Management Architecture. I'm Learning new Updated Stuffs and Enhancing myself to tackle with any Situation or Opportunities . I'd like to think that, together, we can improve the Futuristic Technology to Helps in to Grow the Tech World together.

huzaifakathi2000@gmail.com

7041185934





github.com/HuzaifaDevs007

WORK EXPERIENCE

Flutter Developer Prime Career Academy

02/2020 - 03/2021

Gitanjali Complex, Palace Rd, Dhundhiyawadi, Palanpur, Gujarat 385001

Contact: Sameer Sindhi - 9727054547

Sr. Flutter Developer Webilok IT Services

05/2021 - Present

EDUCATION

H.S.C

Ascent School of Science

06/2017 - 03/2018

Palanpur

Bachelor's of Science in Information Technology

Maktabah Jafariyah College

07/2021 - Present

Maktabah Jafariyah, Sedrana Square, Siddhpur, Gujarat 384151

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Aadesha Auction App (05/2021 - 07/2021)

- Aadesha Auction App is Based on other Auctions Apps Like: E-Auction of Government, Live-Auctioneers etc... Aadesha Auction App is Completely Legal App with Contains Terms & Condition. I Learned Lots of things, Login, Algorithms from this App, it would take 1.2 - 1.5 months to develop this app.

Motima International Concentrator App (07/2021 - 07/2021)

Motima International Concentrator App is Completely based on Ecommerce, in this App we Can Buy, Sell, and little bit info about Oxygen Concentrators.

Shopicart Ecommerce App (07/2021 - Present)

We Developing Completely Ecommerce Based App like:Flipkart, Amazon, etc.

NexMoney Pro (08/2021 - 09/2021)

- This App is Little bit challenging for me, I Learned Almost Advanced Level of Coding From this app State-Management, Data Structures, Algorithms, Coding Structure.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Certification of Software Developer (07/2019 - 07/2020)

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Reading

Dancing

Writing

Coding